## Casey O'Keefe

Full Stack Developer

ocase1990@gmail.com 512-738-4987 ocase1990.github.io www.linkedin.com/in/caseyokeefe512

## **About Me**

I am a dependable, hard working, goal oriented, and determined person. I strive to make the biggest difference I can possibly make when placed in any role in any environment. I consume information daily to ensure myself above competency. I embrace team communication and seek the most effective ways to accomplish tasks efficiently. I research daily on new information that could improve myself and my overall knowledge base. I am a trained and Licensed Paramedic. I am an avid runner and have completed the Austin Marathon.

## Skills

Languages & Frameworks: JavaScript ES6 / ES7, React & Redux, Express, Node.js, MongoDB /Mongoose, jQuery, HTML/CSS/Bootstrap 3 / 4

**Website Design:** Extensive knowledge on website development from consultation to deployment. **Development Best Practices:** Disciplined usage of Git to properly organize project workflow, knowledge of test-driven development protocols such as Mocha.

**Other:** Extensive knowledge of Excel including harvesting data, creating tables, charts, and interactive Excel Dashboards. Firm grasp on programs such as Photoshop and text editors.

## **Experience**

Austin Coding Academy Teacher Assistant January 2018 - Present

- I act as an assistant in teaching students in various levels of coding classes.
- --Utilizing remote access and control of student's computers to teach and show solutions while also using camera and microphones to communicate while the students are not in class.
- --Tutored cohorts through introductory HTML/CSS and JavaScript.
- --Actively contributed to the initial class of students utilizing remote technologies to attend coding classes.

Chat With Me

November 2017 - December 2017

Creator

Simple chat app utilizing firebase storage integration.

--Chat app created with React-Native to chat with other users based on topic of the conversation.

Hideout Coffee House / Theatre Website

March 2017 - June 2017

Co-Creator

Redesigned the website utilizing current HTML/CSS/JavaScript with over 30 pages of content.

--I designed the restructure and wireframe and delegated tasks to my other two team members who were involved.

Education

Austin Coding Academy
Full Stack Web Development

2017

Austin Community College

Associates of Science in Paramedicine 3.5GPA

2010